feelbegin.com 2017-06-06

# 

## Privacy Policy

Last modified: September, 2015 

This Privacy Policy (" **Privacy Policy** " or " **Policy** ") is designed to help You decide whether to use Feelbegin and in what manner. This Policy is incorporated into, subject to and a part of Feelbegin’s Terms of Use, a binding agreement between Feelbegin Software (“Feelbegin Software“, “We” or “Us”), and you, a natural person or a person acting on behalf of a corporation (“You” or “Yourself”). The definitions in the Terms of Use apply to this Policy unless stated otherwise.   
During your use of the Feelbegin Installer delivery and installation platform (“Feelbegin”) for the purpose of installing the Software, Feelbegin gathers certain information from your computer, as detailed below or in the Feelbegin Terms of Use. Feelbegin Software understands You wish to keep your information private, and that You value our emphasis on keeping your information safe and discrete. As a result, We have drafted the Privacy Policy to inform You of the ways in which we gather and use information relating to You and your use of Feelbegin. 

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MAY NOT AND SHOULD NOT USE Feelbegin. 

### Scope of This Privacy Policy

Please note that this Policy governs your use of Feelbegin alone and does not apply to third party services, as well as to third party services incorporated into Feelbegin. This Policy does not relate to any use, storing or gathering of information by The Approved Offers and/or the advertisements that may be presented to You during and after the installation process.   
For information regarding the manner in which said third party software uses your personal information, please refer to their respective privacy policies as they are not provided by Feelbegin. 

### Technical Information

Upon authorizing the installation process, Feelbegin retrieves technical information from your computer such as (without limitation) the type and version of your computer’s operating system, IE browser version and installed hardware, Java resource availability .NET resources availability and your C-Class IP address (the “Technical Information”).   
This Technical Information is used by our servers to provide, maintain and improve the Feelbegin operation and services, such as (without limitation) by verifying that the installed Software and Additional Software are compatible with your computer; by determining which Additional Software and what version should be offered to You and installed on your computer; by correlating errors with certain Technical Information for debugging purposes; and by creating and managing statistics to guide future improvements and developments.   
In addition, the Technical Information is used for Fraud Detection.   
The Technical Information is stored on our servers. 

### Personal Information

We do not collect personal identifiable information (PII) including user name, email address, telephone etc. We may collect none personal identifiable information on an aggregated basis, such as country/region, installed applications etc. in order to improve Feelbegin operation and services and to present You with Offers which are better suited for You. This information is encrypted and stored on our servers. 

### Installation Information

In addition, we may gather information regarding the installation process, including with regard to the Offers presented to You via Feelbegin, The Approved Offers installed on your computer and Technical Information regarding the installation process, such as, without limitation, success/failure, duration, malfunctions, errors, etc. (the “Installation Information”).   
The Installation Information is used to provide, maintain and improve Feelbegin’s operation and services. The Installation Information is shared, in an aggregated form and without any personally identifiable information, with our affiliates for billing and statistical reporting purposes with respect of Feelbegin performance in installing their software (i.e. Software and/or Approved Offers). 

### Cookies

We may use cookies (or equivalents, such as flash cookies or pixels) to correlate between your computer and information stored in our servers. Any information derived from cookie use, shall be treated as Technical Information or Personal Information, as described herein, based on the type of information. 

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

We may share non-personally identifiable information with third parties, when this is required in order to provide, maintain or improve the Feelbegin operation and services. We may NOT share personally identifiable information with any third party, except in an aggregated and/or statistical form.   
We may share your Personal Information and other information in special cases if we have a good reason to belief that it is necessary to: (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, violation of our policies or technical issues; (3) enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy and/or any other agreements between You and Feelbegin Software, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Feelbegin Software, its partners, its affiliates, users and/or the public. 

### No Obligation to Store Information

Nothing in this Policy is interpreted as an obligation to store information, and we may, at our own discretion, delete or avoid from recording and storing any and all information. 

### Children Protection

Regardless of the aforementioned, we do not knowingly collect or store information regarding children under the age of 13 except as permitted under applicable law. 

### Information Warranty Disclaimer

Notwithstanding anything else in this Policy, we are not responsible for the accuracy, correctness and security of any of the information we gather, store and disclose to You or to anyone else. 

### Review and Deletion

We value your privacy and control over your personal information, and therefore You may, at any time, notify us that You wish to either review your personal information or delete it. You can notify us by sending an email to our legal department at [answers@Feelbegin.com](mailto:answers@Feelbegin.com). In order to delete or allow You to review your personal information, we may require that You provide us with identifying information or install additional software to allow such review.   
Inquiry Should You feel that your privacy was invaded or your personal information reached third parties without your authorization, You should contact us immediately in order to allow our legal department to commence an investigation. In such case, You may be required to provide us with additional information in order to allow such inquiry. 

### Data Security

We place great emphasis on the security and integrity of your information and the data stored in our systems.   
Feelbegin is provided under the best commercially reasonable data security practices, in order to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or deletion of any and all information stored in our systems. You acknowledge, however, that no such effort can completely guarantee the security of the stored data, that breaches of security are still a possibility both regarding our systems and that a data security breach resulting in unauthorized access to your information can occur in third party system (for example, ISPs and hosting services providers). As a result, we do NOT warrant or ensure the integrity and security of the data stored in our systems, including without limitation your information.   
We shall notify any user whose information is suspected of being accessed, disclosed, altered or deleted by an unauthorized person, so that he can take appropriate measure to minimize the adverse effect of such a data security breach (Breach Notification). Such Breach Notification will be given in a reasonable time after we learn of said breach, unless we deem, at our sole discretion, that such Notification might hinder and prevent ongoing efforts to detect the source of the breach.   
For the avoidance of doubt, a Breach Notification does NOT constitute an admission by us that the breach occurred as a result of malpractice, failure, bad faith or negligence on our behalf or that the breach even occurred in our systems. 

### Change of Ownership

In the event of a change of ownership or control of all or part of Feelbegin Software, including without limitation through acquisition, merger or sale, we reserve the right to assign all or part of the personal information we store in our systems.   
You acknowledge that in the event of bankruptcy, insolvency or receivership, we may have no control over the use and transfer of your personal information. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Policy may be revised from time to time at our sole discretion. The last revision will be reflected in the “Last modified” heading above.
